[{"answer": " Well, actually, we have a little black boy named He", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " That's right, my friend, I'm headed for that place on a whisperin' jet", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "But who were they", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "In what sense were they bad", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "They were just bad men, that's all", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Bad is bad, my friend. There ain't no sense to it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Your Daddy is a wonderful man, I'll say that. He's the best and most kin", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What terrible thing in Cave Springs", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, I know", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I do, too", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, I don't know, I... I..", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " I... I'll get the grits", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You look sick if you ask me. I hate to leave you with the dishes and all, but I'm supposed to go to a meeting of the Garden Club this evening.  I'll need the car keys", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I think about what I'm doing all the time, and I've got as much business behind the wheel of an automobile as anybody. Besides, I want you to stay and help my friend with the dishes, the poor girl isn't feeling well", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Wow! Brrrother", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Buddy, this is amazing, you wouldn't believe it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What are they doing", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What are they doing, Doll", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But Rose..", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Am I hurting you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Don't worry, my friend, I won't tell a soul", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Good night, my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I know, my friend", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I am in awe of it, my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " You're so sweet", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Why, sure, always got time to get you a hal", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Forgive my crudity, my friend'. All I'm saying is that a girl who would wear clothes like that is going to get in trouble sooner or later", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, darlin', time will tell", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So am I", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " It isn't that she hasn't got any sense, Doll. Her basic intelligence is probably above average, maybe quite a bit above average", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'd like to ask you the same question, you bastard", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You got no right to tell me to stay away from her, I knew her before you did", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, my sleep was a little disturbed last night, and so was Mrs. my friend's, and so was the children's. How about you? Was your sleep disturbed, too", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Strange voices, my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, shut up, my friend. Shut your mouth and quit crying", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I am not being brutal to her", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I am not being brutal to her", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " my friend', it is not my fault if the girl has epizootics", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Nurse says we have a nervous patient. Now, young lady, be calm. First of all, let me tell you, I am not going to hurt you", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No, I am not", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, what have you got to say for yourself", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": " That's all you've got to say, you've got a bad cold", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Of course she does and I must say I'm puzzled by your delay in getting her to the hospital. I should think ordinary powers of observation would have suggested to you that she was seriously ill", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Afraid of the hospital", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yeah, he tried to hide it but I saw 'em, and a little bit he says to me,", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "He's got doubts about hisself and that's the saddest thing of all. Would you believe that poor man thinks nobody likes him", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " What do you think, my friend", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "He's not coming back again. We scared the rascal off, son.  Come on back to supper. Your mother has a theory about how to educate my friend", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Her plan is obvious, plain as day. She's going on a hunger strike. The question is, how do we foil her", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Something has got to be done or my friend is going to be in this house forever", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": " Well, I have got news! I called long distance and spoke to Cousin Hop and you'll be glad to know, my friend, I have found you a job", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yes, that place, a lovely state", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes, that place, a lovely state", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Ah", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": " Poor thing, don't cry, my friend. I know you feel awful, but don't cry, honey, nobody's perfect. Who's the father, dear", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " I know it's embarrassing... but who were you exposed to, dear? ROSE Well, now, Mrs. my friend, I... a", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "She's an adult, Mrs. my friend, I was merely giving her the facts", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Any major operation is dangerous. However, as we know from her previous illness, she's a very strong girl", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Yes, we know her", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Rose isn't oversexed, that's ridiculous. If you're going to talk nonsense, I don't want to talk to you at all. Rose is exactly the same as the rest of us, except more so", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " Better off? How could she ever find love and happiness, if you did what you're talking about? Are you insane", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": " Yeah, I know, he was up here. It's pitiful like you say. When he lost my friend it ruined the man, it destroyed him totally when he lost my friend", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Yes, I guess he did. He threw her away and it was the mistake of his life", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "All right, Daddy. We have our drink, we're out on the patio, you have prepared me for it. my friend's cancer has come back, hasn't it", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": " Dead, my friend is dead? You mean... she died", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": " I know. You loved her. So did I. It was an awful shock to me, too. An awful shock. my friend was so alive it's hard to believe", "docId": "Rambling-Rose.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "It's true, son. The girl with the cornflower eyes is dead, she is no more", "qsentId": 68}]